They're here for drama promotion.
Dia datang untuk syuting.
Go! Good luck!
Maju, Daji.
Go!
Maju!
Pull one in.
Seret masuk satu.
Yuwen.
Yuwen.
Go! Good luck!
Semangat, Daji.
Come on, good luck!
Semangat!
Yang Chaoyue.
Yang Chaoyue.
They're here for drama promotion, Yang Chaoyue.
Dia datang untuk syuting drama, Yang Chaoyue.
So embarrassing.
Sangat memalukan.
Chaoyue.
Chaoyue.
Anyu.
Anyu.
Did I see that right?
Aku tidak salah lihat, 'kan?
Three shots in a row.
Tiga tembakan berturut-turut.
Anyu.
An Yu.
Same fate as Wang Yuwen.
Berakhir seperti Wang Yuwen.
Dragged Wang Anyu for a kilometer.
Dia menarik Wang Anyu untuk membajak tanah seluas 2 mil.
Why are you all mocking me like this?
Atas dasar apa kalian menertawakanku?
Stop humiliating them.
Jangan "mempermalukan" mereka lagi.
They're here for drama promotion.
Dia datang untuk mengumumkan.
I'm never coming to Changsha again.
Ke depannya aku tidak akan datang ke Changsha.
I'm never coming to this show again.
Acara kalian ini tidak akan datang lagi.
Chaoyue is really strong.
Tenaga Chaoyue sangat besar.
Yang Chaoyue.
Yang Chaoyue.
So strong.
Hebat.
Her face is all red.
Wajahnya sudah merah.
Yang Chaoyue.
Yang Chaoyue.
Winning is also a sign of respect for our opponents.
Kita menang juga merupakan rasa hormat terhadap lawan.
Give it your all.
Lakukan yang terbaik.
We must give it everything we've got.
Harus berusaha sekuat tenaga.
Miaoyi.
Miao Yi
They're here for drama promotion, Yang Chaoyue.
Dia adalah Yang Chaoyue.
I know you're feeling hopeless right now, Miaoyi.
Aku tahu kau sangat putus asa, Miao Yi.
Wait a second.
Tunggu sebentar.
Yang Chaoyue.
Yang Chaoyue.
What are you doing?
Ada apa?
Why are you so strong?
Kenapa tenagamu besar sekali?
You can only use one hand.
Hanya bisa menggunakan satu tangan
She's pulling me with both hands.
Kedua tangannya menarikku.
She can't hear clearly.
Dia tidak bisa mendengarnya dengan jelas.
Tell her to put her hands behind her back.
Katanya tangannya sampai di belakang,
She heard it and dislocated her hand.
Dia dengar tangannya terkilir,
Draw! Hurry, draw!
Cepat tarik.
Pretty manager.
Manajer toko yang cantik.
One hand.
Satu tangan.
They're here for drama promotion.
Mereka datang untuk syuting.
They're from "Brotherly Love and Sisterly Respect".
"Saudara, Teman, Adik"
Show it.
Buka.
Draw against him.
Pukul dia.
He didn't show it.
Dia tidak menunjukkannya.
They're here for drama promotion.
Dia datang untuk syuting drama.
He's doing it again.
Dia begini lagi
Please have Xu Zhisheng demonstrate a move.
Persilakan Xu Zhi Sheng untuk menunjukkan gerakannya.
This is my move.
Gerakan ini.
Seven thirty.
Pukul 07.30.
After the scramble.
Setelah berebut,
Two heads.
Dua kepala.
Chaoyue.
Chaoyue.
He's doing it again.
Dia begini lagi.
We have to win.
Kita harus menang.
They're here for drama promotion.
Mereka datang untuk mengumumkan.
"The Ideal Son-in-law" is here for drama promotion.
"The Legend" datang untuk mengumumkan.
"The Ideal Son-in-law".
"Daftar Pasangan Bahagia".
"The Ideal Son-in-law" drama promotion.
Pengumuman drama "Daftar Pasangan Bahagia".
We'll help them promote.
Kita bantu mereka umumkan.
Help them promote.
Bantu mereka umumkan.
Support "The Ideal Son-in-law".
Dukung "Daftar Calon Mertua".
Time's up.
Waktunya tiba.
We have to win.
Kita harus menang.
The defense is really fierce.
Pertahanannya sangat kuat.
The mouth fell off.
Mulut lepas semua.
Mouth? Whose mouth fell off?
Mulut? Mulut siapa?
What's going on?
Apa yang terjadi?
Quick, Xin Hao, go!
Cepat, Xinhao maju.
Xin Hao, we can't lose.
Xinhao, kita tidak boleh kalah.
Xin Hao.
Xinhao.
Xin Hao, you got this.
Xin Hao boleh saja.
Wait, why is he so fast?
Bukan, kenapa dia begitu cepat
He can still stand up.
Dia masih bisa berdiri.
My hand can't get out.
Tanganku tidak bisa keluar.
Because his hand can't get out.
Karena dia tidak bisa keluar.
Okay, Xin Hao has finished eating.
Baik, Xinhao sudah selesai makan.
Copy that bug, yes.
Pelajari serangga itu. Benar.
That's right.
Benar.
What kind of bug is this?
Cacing apa ini?
We have to win.
Kita harus menang.
Win.
Menang.
Chaoyue.
Chaoyue.
Use strength.
Da Li.
Yang Chaoyue.
Yang Chaoyue.
What is this, Yang Chaoyue?
Ini apa? Yang Chaoyue.
Tackle.
Bucket.
You really deserve to be called Chaoyue.
Kau benar-benar layak menjadi Chaoyue.
They haven't won a single game today.
Mereka tidak pernah memenangkan satu babak permainan hari ini.
Yeah.
Benar.
Not a single win.
Satu babak tidak menang.
I'm done, bro.
Tidak, Kak.
Tian Jiarui, come here.
Tian Jiarui, mari.
White rabbits have white bellies.
Kelinci putih perut putih.
Black rabbits have black bellies.
Kelinci hitam adalah perut hitam.
White rabbits are white.
Kelinci putih.
Rabbit.
Kelinci?
Rabbit what?
Kelinci apa?
Stop with the rabbit.
Jangan kelinci lagi.
You're still this slow?
Kau sudah selambat ini, masih...
Rabbit.
Kelinci?
Our IQs...
Iq kita berdua
...basically say goodbye to this game.
Pada dasarnya mengucapkan selamat tinggal pada game ini.
Seriously.
Sungguh.
I give up.
Aku mengaku kalah.
Sorry.
Maaf.
Why did I say that?
Kenapa aku mengatakan ini?
Slide out.
Kau tergelincir keluar,
Slide out with your foot.
Gunakan kakimu untuk meluncur keluar.
Use the top of your foot, not your heel.
Meluncur dengan punggung kaki, bukan dengan tumit.
Top of your foot, slide out with it.
Kaki lepas, kaki lepas.
Twisted my ankle.
Kaki terkilir.
It's broken.
Patah tulang.
After sliding with your left foot, use your right.
Setelah kaki kiri meluncur, kaki kanan meluncur.
Top of the foot.
Punggung kaki.
Top of the foot—where's your "back"?
Punggung kaki? Punggungmu di mana?
Top of the foot?
Punggung kaki?
The back?
Punggung tidak?
Your foot's top is crooked.
Punggung kakimu miring.
Can you tell where the top of your foot is?
Apakah kau bisa membedakan mana punggung kaki?
What is this?
Ini apa?
My scalp feels cold.
Kulit kepala dingin,
Xu Weizhou.
Xu Weizhou.
Zhuzhu.
Zhu.
Right in the face.
Tepat di depan pintu.
What's this?
Apa ini?
Scared but still grabbing like crazy.
Takut dan panik.
Wait a second.
Tunggu sebentar.
Grab.
Tangkap!
What is this thing?
Benda apa ini?
It has legs and antennae.
Ada kaki dan tentakel.
I think it's moving.
Aku merasa dia bergerak.
Where is this? What is it?
Ini di mana? Ini apa?
You touched its antenna.
Kau sudah menyentuh tentakel-nya?
No way.
Tidak bisa.
Not this one.
Ini jangan.
Don't want it.
Jangan.
No.
Tidak.
Don't want it.
Jangan!
What is this?
Apa ini?
Impressive.
Hebat.
Don't want it.
Jangan.
It just came out.
Tadi sudah keluar.
Throw—throw me.
Lempar aku.
Failed again.
Lagi-lagi gagal.
Okay.
Baik.
No.
Tidak bisa.
You can't throw like that.
Kau tidak boleh melempar seperti ini.
How should I throw?
Bagaimana caranya aku melempar?
Sorry.
Maaf.
You can't do that.
Kau tidak boleh seperti ini.
You can flip me backward.
Kau bisa membalikkanku ke belakang,
But you can't say that.
Namun, kau tidak boleh bilang begitu.
Yeah, do it like this.
Benar, harus seperti ini.
Need to get over.
Harus ke sana.
On top of the shoulder.
Di bahu.
Alright.
Baik.
What is this?
Ini apa?
A brand new pose.
Postur yang baru.
No, can't get through.
Tidak bisa.
Hold on, you have to hold.
Harus digendong.
Still have to hold.
Masih harus dipeluk.
We look good.
Kita cantik.
Fix your hair, Guan Yue.
Rapikan juga gaya rambut dan musik.
One, two, three, go.
Satu, dua, tiga, jalan.
We must look good.
Harus cantik.
Throw it over.
Lempar ke sana.
Look good when you go over.
Masa lalu harus indah.
No, can't get through.
Tidak bisa, tidak bisa.
You can't do it.
Kau tidak bisa.
You didn't throw your upper body.
Tubuh bagian atasmu tidak melempar.
I'm telling you, it's the upper body.
Kuberi tahu, tubuh bagian atas.
Your body.
Tubuh...
One, two, three.
Satu, dua, tiga.
Go, this way.
Ayo, sebelah sini.
Go.
Jalan.
Are you okay?
Tidak apa-apa kan?
Guan Yue.
Musik tiup.
Hurry.
Cepat.
Okay.
Baik.
It's done.
Sudah cukup.
Pass the ball.
Oper bolanya.
Zheng Ting.
Zhengting.
Stop.
Berhenti.
That's not right.
Salah.
Come quickly, hurry.
Cepat kemari.
Tian Jiarui.
Tian Jiarui.
Time to show your genius.
Sudah saatnya menunjukkan kejeniusannya.
I think...
Menurutku,
It has to come.
Harus datang.
Because when I pulled out my hand,
Karena saat aku mengeluarkannya,
it looked a lot like bro's.
Sangat mirip dengan Kakak.
But...
Tetapi,
When Hu Xianxu pulled out his hand,
Begitu tangan Hu Xianxu dikeluarkan,
there were black sesame seeds on it.
Di atasnya ada biji wijen hitam.
No.
Bukan.
It's because the cloth faded.
Kain ini yang telah hilang warnanya.
Genius.
Orang berbakat.
No.
Bukan.
The fuzz on this cloth.
Bola bulu di kain ini
Not that fuzz.
Bukan bola bulu itu.
Look.
Lihatlah.
No.
Tidak.
Yes.
Ada.
You have fuzz too.
Kau juga punya bola bulu?
How come you...
Kau kenapa?
This undercover...
Mata-mata ini,
is just here to mess things up.
Hanya membuat kekacauan.
Forget what I said.
Anggap aku tidak mengatakannya.
Wait a second.
Tunggu.
Jiarui.
Jiarui.
I'm telling you, it's definitely three.
Kuberi tahu, pasti tiga.
Trust me.
Percayalah padaku.
My lucky number is three.
Angka keberuntunganku adalah tiga.
You have to trust me.
Kau harus percaya padaku.
Three is chosen.
Tiga pilihan.
Did we choose three?
Apakah kita sudah memilih tiga?
Wait, sorry.
Maaf nanti.
Three isn't there.
Tiga, tidak.
Three.
Tiga.
Wait, don't pick three.
Tunggu, jangan tiga.
I'll wait a moment.
Aku tunggu sebentar.
Still not yet.
Masih tidak mau?
Don't choose three.
Jangan tiga.
Pick three.
Tiga.
Hold on.
Tunggu sebentar.
Go with three.
Tunggu, kita tidak mau tiga lagi.
Not three again? Say it again.
Jangan tiga lagi, kau katakan lagi.
Number three.
Tiga.
Choose.
Pilih.
I'm telling you, number three just now already
Kuberi tahu kau, mereka nomor tiga tadi sudah
was about to bring it over.
Postur yang akan dibawa kemari.
Stop talking about it.
Kau jangan bicara lagi.
Really?
Benarkah?
Let's eliminate number three first, okay?
Nomor tiga hilangkan dulu.
That's not right.
Salah.
Seriously, you...
Kau benar-benar
She just did it like this.
Tadi dia langsung begini.
She was just trying to scare you.
Dia menakutimu
They're eager, you know?
Mereka tidak sabar menunggu, kau mengerti?
Jiarui, you're a genius at games.
Jiarui, kau adalah genius dalam permainan.
Bro, listen to me.
Kak, dengarkan aku.
Number three is a dud.
Nomor tiga adalah melon.
Don't mess it up.
Kau jangan berantakan.
I'm not messing it up.
Aku tidak berantakan.
I took notes.
Aku membuat catatan.
Number three.
Nomor tiga.
Check the notes.
Lihatlah catatanmu.
Okay, I'll check the notes.
Baik, aku lihat catatan.
It's the only one left.
Hanya tersisa dia.
It's a bit confusing.
Agak kacau.
No, I wanted to give it to you, bro.
Bukan, aku sudah ingin memberikannya padamu, Kak.
It's definitely three.
Pasti tiga.
Let's go with three.
Hanya tiga?
No.
Bukan.
On their side, it should be four.
Seharusnya mereka bernomor empat.
If four is a bottle of Zhenguoli,
Keempat adalah sebotol Zhenguoli,
Three bottles.
Tiga botol.
Three.
Tiga.
Jiarui.
Jiarui.
Four.
Empat.
Give it to him.
Berikan dia
Top it up.
Perbaiki.
Top it up again.
Tambah nutrisi.
It's fine now.
Tidak apa-apa.
Wait, two bottles are already here.
Nanti dua botol sudah habis.
Three.
Tiga.
Alright, okay.
Baik.
Tian.
Tian.
Genius.
Genius.
Three.
Tiga.
Wait a moment.
Tunggu sebentar.
Bro.
Kak.
Genius.
Genius.
I'm about to win.
Aku akan segera menang.
Genius, MVP.
Anggota tim berbakat yang paling berharga
Bro, wait a second.
Kak, kau tunggu sebentar.
MVP.
Anggota yang paling berharga
Bro, wait a second, I'm almost done.
Kak, tunggu sebentar, aku segera...
You've already taken seven or eight bottles.
Kau sudah mengambil tujuh sampai delapan botol.
There aren't many buns left, take a break.
Mantou juga tidak banyak, kau istirahat saja.
I really love watching
Aku sangat suka melihat
Tian Jiarui thinking.
Cara berpikir Tian Jiarui.
It's so charming.
Sangat menawan.
Does this get points?
Apakah ini sebanding?
Does this one get points?
Apakah ini ada bagian?
Yes, it does.
Ada perbedaan?
No, he laughed.
Tidak, dia tersenyum.
No.
Salah.
The first box
Kotak pertama.
I think so
Seharusnya begitu.
Let him choose
Biarkan dia memilih.
There are points
Ada perbedaan.
Teacher Sha
Guru Sha.
Yes, right here
Di sini.
Can you give me some advice?
Berikan aku sebuah saran, oke?
If we want to play longer,
Jika kita harus bermain lebih lama,
I suggest not picking number one
Aku rasa sebaiknya jangan pilih satu.
If you pick one, you lose all your points, right?
Pilih satu, kalian semua akan habis?
Not exactly
Bukan juga.
You can choose
Kau boleh pilih.
Just sit at number one
Duduk saja.
Come on
Mari.
How is it?
Bagaimana?
This round of analysis
Analisis gelombang ini
Eighty
Delapan puluh.
So impressive
Hebat sekali.
Big hammer eighty
Palu besar 80.
Eighty
Delapan puluh.
Was my analysis wrong?
Apakah analisisku salah?
So awesome
Hebat sekali.
You're a genius
Kau pintar.
Ninety items
Sembilan puluh porsi.
Ninety
Sembilan puluh.
Highlight moment, genius
Orang genius di momen kejayaan.
Dan bro, am I a real genius this round?
Kak Dan, bukankah aku ini benar-benar berbakat?
Truly a genius
Benar-benar berbakat
Give me a crown
Memberiku sebuah mahkota
After Tian Jiarui's thorough analysis
Setelah analisis Tian Jiarui yang cermat,
This round
Kali ini,
Le Tan now has
Jumlah barang di Le Cha saat ini adalah
one hundred ninety items
Seratus sembilan puluh
Genius
Orang berbakat.
We can turn the tables with just these two pieces
Kita bisa membalikkan keadaan hanya dengan dua catur ini.
How is this possible?
Kenapa ini...
How come?
Ini...
What is this?
Ini apa?
Where did it hit?
Sudah sampai mana?
Xu Zhisheng also had a trick up his sleeve
Xu Zhisheng juga menyembunyikan sesuatu.
Impressive
Hebat
Fabricate out of thin air
Mengada-ada.
Without realizing it
Tanpa sadar
I've already drawn one
Aku sudah mendapat satu.
Come on
Ini.
Get ready here
Bersiaplah di sini.
Put it back for me
Masukkan kembali.
Who is the real sneaky artist?
Siapa sebenarnya artis yang "dicuri"?
I was too embarrassed to say
Aku tidak berani mengatakannya.
He confessed himself
Aku sendiri yang menjelaskan.
Deduct one vote from them
Kurangi suara mereka.
You started sneaking before the match
Sebelum pertandingan, kau sudah mulai "mencuri".
You really have no shame
Kau benar-benar tidak tahu malu.
I thought there was another big twist
Aku kira ada beban besar apa lagi.
Alright, let's count
Baik, mari kita hitung
The scores of both sides
Rekor dua pihak.
One
Satu.
Two
Dua.
Three
Tiga.
Four
Empat.
Five
Lima.
Six
Enam.
Seven
Tujuh.
Why?
Mengapa?
They had one time
Mereka pernah sekali
They took two papers at once
Sekali mengambil dua lembar kertas.
Do you want to tell others something?
Apakah kau ingin memberi tahu orang lain sesuatu?
Or just let them watch it later?
Atau suruh mereka pulang lihat?
Watch it later
Pulang dan lihatlah.
Alright, watch it later
Baik, kembali dan lihatlah.
Why did you lose?
Kenapa kalian kalah?
Well, how should I put it
Bagaimana mengatakannya?
The bros just have more life experience
Kakak-kakak hanya punya sedikit pengalaman sosial.
Did they take from our bowl?
Mereka mengambilnya dari mangkuk kita, benar?
Dige
Kak Di.
Alright
Boleh.
Come back quickly
Cepat kembali.
Remember to watch the show later
Ingat kembali menonton acara.
This is how the show does drama promotion
Acara ini diumumkan seperti ini.
By this episode, we're not promoting dramas anymore
Sampai di episode ini, kita tidak perlu mengumumkan lagi.
Under Yang Chaoyue's leadership
Di bawah pimpinan Yang Chaoyue.
Chaoyue is still cheating
Chaoyue masih menyontek.
But it doesn't seem to help
Tapi rasanya juga tidak ada gunanya.
No, Dige here
Bukan, Kak Di, ini...
Stop
Hentikan.
Just two
Dua.
Four
Empat.
Can the three of you give us some info?
Bisakah kalian bertiga memberi kami sedikit informasi?
He has a pair of agile feet
Dia memiliki sepasang kaki yang fleksibel.
Yes
Benar.
His chewing muscles are well developed
Otot kunyah sangat berkembang.
Chen Xinhao
Chen Xinhao.
There's wind
Ada angin.
No need to say anything.
Tidak perlu dikatakan lagi.
It's Tian Jiarui.
Tian Jiarui.
Not this bro.
Bukan kakak ini.
Can you just...
Bisakah kau memakai sedikit lebih nyaman?
Come on, put it on.
Ayo, pakai.
Chaoyue, why are you...
Chaoyue, kenapa kau...
What's with that face, Chaoyue?
Ekspresi apa? Chaoyue?
She wants to quit the show.
Dia ingin keluar dari acara ini.
I got a little scared when he popped out.
Saat dia keluar, aku sedikit takut.
If you say that, I'll really go over.
Jika kau berkata begitu, aku akan pergi.
Let you get desensitized quickly.
Menyuruhmu melepaskan diri secepat mungkin
One on the left, one on the right.
Sebelah kiri satu, sebelah kanan satu
Come here.
Kemari.
Bro.
Kakak.
Why is the Smile Team fighting internally?
Xiao Neng, kenapa pertikaian internal?
For your flight.
Demi penerbanganmu,
Seven thirty.
Pukul 07.30.
Chaoyue.
Chaoyue.
No.
Jangan.
Sleep.
Tidurlah.
My bun.
Baksoku.
My hairpiece.
Rambut palsu
Xu Zhisheng's bangs are back again.
Poni Xu Zhi Sheng muncul lagi
All the hairpieces got knocked off.
Rambut palsu juga sudah di gugurkan
All the buns got squashed.
Baksonya sudah hampir rata
You four are a team.
Kalian berempat satu tim
Can we check with the others?
Bisakah kita menghadapi orang lain?
We're a team.
Kita satu tim.
Check your clothes, okay?
Kalian lihat pakaian yang kalian pakai.
Right.
Benar.
My hairpiece ended up like this.
Aku sudah pakai wig.
Now you tell me we're a team.
Sekarang kau bilang aku satu tim.
You can't tell at all.
Sama sekali tidak terlihat.
Chaoyue's army.
Melampaui pasukan,
United as one.
Bersatu,
So weird.
Terlalu aneh.
I'm so glad I came here.
Aku sangat beruntung datang ke sini
Go, Zhisheng!
Semangat Zhi Sheng
Huang Zihongfan seems...
Huang Zi Hongfan sepertinya
You're actually not as good as him.
Kau memang tidak sebaik dia.
Your face is all red.
Wajahmu sudah memerah.
Where's the scallion?
Di mana bawang merahnya?
Our scallion.
Bawang merah kita.
Alright.
Sudah.
This round is over.
Babak ini selesai.
Go find a hole and crawl in yourself.
Kau cari lubang untuk bersembunyi.
Huang Zihongfan.
Huang Zi, Hongfan.
I'm the king of this game.
Aku adalah raja game ini.
I'm the queen of this game.
Aku adalah ratu game ini
King and queen.
Raja dan ratu.
Come on, jump.
Lompat.
Hit my face, hit my mouth.
Kau memukulku?
Here it comes.
Sudah datang.
There's one more.
Masih ada satu.
Darn it.
Celaka.
What does that mean?
Apa maksudnya?
It's blocked.
Tersumbat.
Wait a second.
Tunggu sebentar.
Is it me?
Apakah ini aku?
Wait, no.
Tidak bisa.
It's you.
Itu kau.
You have to make up for this variety show effect.
Hasil variety show ini pasti akan kutambahkan.
Hurry up.
Cepat.
Let's cut and redo it.
Silakan hentikan dan mulai lagi.
How unlucky am I.
Betapa sengsaranya aku.
I worked so hard to trick him here.
Aku sudah menghabiskan banyak waktu untuk menipunya sampai di sini.
Hurry up.
Cepat.
Wait a second.
Tunggu sebentar.
Right away.
Segera.
Dige.
Kak Di.
Dobby.
Dobby.
I'm Dobby.
Aku adalah Dobby.
My life is so tough.
Hidupku sangat menderita
My life.
Nyawaku.
You two sit here.
Kalian berdua duduk di sini.
You sit.
Kau duduk.
Where?
Di mana?
You sit, sit down.
Duduk.
I'm sitting here again.
Aku duduk di sini lagi.
Yeah, you sit here.
Benar, kau duduk di sini.
Then I...
Kalau begitu, aku...
That won't work.
Tidak bisa.
Then I'll sit.
Kalau begitu, aku duduk.
No, that's not it.
Bukan.
No, this spot is just like this.
Tidak, posisinya memang seperti ini.
Wait, let me ask Wang Qiang.
Bukan, aku tanya Wang Qiang.
Yes.
Benar.
Is the (safe seat) gone?
[Tempat duduk aman] Apakah sudah tidak ada?
Wang Qiang told me the (safe seat) is gone.
Wang Qiang bilang tempat duduknya sudah tidak ada.
There's one.
Ada satu
You have to fight him.
Kau bertarung dengannya
Only with him.
Hanya bisa bersamanya
Stand up.
Bangun.
If this game ends
Jika permainan ini sudah selesai,
and Chen Xinhao doesn't get sprayed,
Chen Xinhao tidak tersemprot,
then I'm really good.
Maka aku hebat.
I won't film next episode.
Aku tidak akan syuting episode berikutnya.
It's fine, film next time.
Tidak apa-apa, lain kali rekam lagi.
Stand up for a second.
Bangun sebentar.
I'm not getting up.
Aku tidak bangun.
Because you have plenty now.
Karena sekarang kau sangat hebat.
It's okay.
Tidak apa-apa.
Dige, go away.
Kak Di, kau pergi.
You still...
Kau masih...
Are you coming here?
Bukankah kau sudah tidur?
Bro, I fell asleep.
Aku sudah tidur, Kak.
No way.
Tidak bisa.
Not exciting.
Tidak seru.
This is boring, yeah.
Ini tidak menarik. Benar.
It should be a "smack" right on your face.
Seharusnya "Plak" menutupi wajahmu.
Yeah.
Benar.
Then "smack," it sticks here.
Lalu, menempel di sini.
That piece covers your face.
Kulit di wajah.
Yeah, covers your eyes.
Benar, tutup di mata.
"Smack!"
Plak!
So fun.
Seru sekali.
I want to ask.
Aku ingin bertanya,
Where's our show's special effects teacher?
Di mana guru efek khusus acara kita?
I have something to say to him.
Ada yang ingin aku bicarakan dengannya.
Thank you all.
Aku berterima kasih pada kalian.
Just you two.
Hanya kalian berdua?
You two can do so many bad things.
Kalian bisa melakukan begitu banyak hal jahat,
How did you manage it step by step?
Bagaimana melakukannya selangkah demi selangkah
Put a shooting thing in my mouth.
Dan menaruh pistol di mulutku?
Thanks to the teachers.
Terima kasih para Mentor.
Great, really awesome.
Bisa, sangat hebat.
Say something trending again.
Satu lagi, jika masuk pencarian populer,
Is there anything...
Apa ada...
What kind of editing is this?
Apa yang kau potong?
You're done for, Xu Zhisheng.
Habislah kau, Xu Zhisheng.
Tell the audience.
Beritahu para penonton
Xu Zhisheng is censored here.
Yang memberi kode di sini adalah Xu Zhisheng.
Why is it censored?
Kenapa harus menggunakan kode?
The reason is just now.
Alasannya karena tadi
Maybe he said something.
Mungkin dia mengatakan sesuatu.
He offended the post-production teacher.
Dia telah menyinggung guru belakangan ini.
Now he's censored.
Sekarang dia sudah diberi kode,
Doesn't matter what happens to him now.
Tidak masalah apa yang kau lakukan padanya.
Alright.
Baik.
So today,
Kalau begitu hari ini kita
all the mid-year awards are finished.
Semua seleksi tahunan akan berakhir.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Congratulations, Dige.
Selamat kepada Kak Di,